capitalone.co.uk 2016-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Legal Information - Capital One

## FOR THOSE WHO LIKE THE DETAIL

Capital One's privacy policy applies to anyone who visits our websites. It explains how we may collect information from you online when you visit a Capital One website and how we may protect and use that information. Therefore, please read this privacy policy carefully before using the websites.

In this privacy policy, "we", "us", "our" and "Capital One" means Capital One (Europe) plc and "you" and "your" means the individual who is using the websites. Information that you provide to Capital One when you apply for or obtain a credit card from us is also governed by the "Use of your information" section at clause 1 of your credit card agreement, which is also set out in our online application form. If you are an applicant or customer, please refer to the application form or credit card agreement for additional information. In the event of a conflict between the terms of this Privacy Policy and your credit card agreement, your credit card agreement shall take precedence.

### Collecting information

#### Information you provide

Capital One may collect information that you provide when completing forms on its websites, for example an application for a credit card, a survey or a competition.

#### Information gathered from your use of our websites

Capital One may collect the following information about you when you browse our websites or use our online services:

We may collect technical information about your browser and the pages that you visit. For example we may collect your internet protocol (IP) address, which is a numerical identifier assigned to a computer or device that connects to the internet.

We may use cookies and other online tracking devices to maintain your user session and track browsing activities conducted with your computer. For further information, please read the Capital One Cookie Policy.

### How we use information

#### On our websites

We may use cookies, web beacons or similar devices to help us understand which parts of our site you find most useful and to optimise your browsing experience. For full details, check our cookie policy.

If you choose, you can set your browser to inform you when cookies are sent or you may choose not to accept cookies. If you haven't done this, our system will issue cookies when you visit the site.

#### Sharing information

We may share information that we collect online or as part of any application with companies within the Capital One Group which means us, our ultimate holding company and any company which is a subsidiary of our ultimate holding company; and with companies that provide services to us, including sub-contractors, agents or other companies including those based outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

We may also share this information with third parties, in a secure manner, for the purposes of targeting or exclusion from our marketing activity, or to help us contact you with regards to your account. Your data will not be shared or sold to third parties for use in their marketing activities or email lists.

We may partner with third parties to deliver advertisements and surveys and to monitor activities on our own websites and other websites. You'll find full details in our cookie policy.

### Capital One online services

Capital One offers its customers online account services. When you register for those services, we will provide you with specific terms and conditions that may supplement the information in this notice. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use Capital One's online account services.

### Links

Our websites may include links to third-party websites. These third parties are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Whenever you visit a third-party website, you should review its privacy notice. We do not accept any responsibility for any such third party websites, including without limitation for their accuracy, security, the products or services which they offer or any information which is collected through them.

### Data security

At Capital One, we make your safety and security a top priority and are committed to protecting your personal and financial information. If we collect personal information from you, we will protect that information with controls based upon internationally recognised security standards, regulations, and industry-based best practices.

Capital One maintains customer authentication procedures to protect your personal information and account from identity theft. These procedures are for your protection. If you suspect a website is "spoofing" or pretending to be a Capital One website do not enter personal information but instead contact us through the details set out in the contact us page or by emailing [abuse@capitalone.com](mailto:abuse@capitalone.com).

If you receive an email that claims to be from us but you are not sure, or if you think it is suspicious, do not click on any of the links in the e-mail. Instead forward it to us at [abuse@capitalone.com](mailto:abuse@capitalone.com) then delete it.

For more information about our commitment to security and for tips about what you can do to help guard against fraud and identity theft, visit our Security Centre.

### Your rights Accessing your personal information

You have a right under the Data Protection Act 1998 upon written request and payment of a fee, to have a copy of the personal data we hold about you. If you would like to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you please write to us at the address shown in contact us.

#### Opting out of receiving marketing material

You have a right under the Data Protection Act 1998 to ask us not to process your personal data or pass it to third parties for marketing purposes. If you do not want to receive marketing material from us or third parties please write to us at the address shown in contact us.
